Well, it has begun, Upgod. This time we have Akari Uemura of Juice Juice and Nanami Kubota of Ochanoma.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Let's start with the two MCs.
I, Uemura, think that now that we are able to speak out, we get a lot more calls at our live performances,
I myself, Uemura, have always been a person who does not sweat much on my face. During the past three years.
Oh, really?
But after I started to be able to speak out, I started to sweat so much that it was almost a lie,
Yume Kudo used to be a sweaty girl who splashed around a lot, so I was a little bothered by it,
But when I put myself in her shoes, I realized that this was how I felt, and it was a lot of fun.
It was really hot, partly because it was summer, and I could really feel the heat of the live performance in my body,
So I would like to continue to control my sweat so that it doesn't become a nuisance.
It is true that I have an image of you always staying clean without sweating.
I kind of thought so myself, but I guess I was wrong.
Are you saying that one day you will suddenly become one?
Yes, that's right.
Neither of us are the type to sweat.
I've recovered my sweating as well as my voice, so I'd like to adjust it.
Yes, I, Kubota, have recently started thinking one day that I want to have a beautiful back,
A back beauty.
I started to do some stretches before going to bed to make my back beautiful.
I started doing back stretches before going to bed.
I stretch my back for about five to seven minutes, and it seems to relieve my stiff shoulders,
I have been doing it for about a week now, and my shoulders have become a little softer.
It's great that my shoulders feel better just by having a cleaner shoulder line.
Then I think I'll start this summer too.
Let's start with this time's up-kami, here's the making of Angulum's Alumni music video shoot.
Here is the making of the music video for "Alumni" from Angulum's latest single.
Here is the making of the music video.
Here's the making of the music video shooting for "Alumni.
Let's start with the up-cam.
Alumni are great, aren't they?
It's nice to be able to get together again, isn't it?
I mean, there's been a lot of graduations and other stuff, but...
But I've always loved Ange.
I like that.
You know, I love these girls.
The juniors are cute, too.
No matter what time of day it is.
They're so cute.
Oh, he's cute.
Which one do you like better?
I think I like the one on the iPhone better.
This one looks like a bus for me, too.
Oh, wow.
It's just like Ricocollo's.
Cute!
Cute.
It's some kind of back cut.
It's cute.
It's a back cut, but it looks good.
Yes, we're shooting a music video for Alumni right now.
As you can already see, this is my outfit from the last Big Love album.
It's that dirty!
The theme of this year's music video is to decorate with everyone.
We painted a lot of pictures with paint.
It's not often that we get to paint on costumes like this, so it was a lot of fun!
It's so much fun!
If you look over there, you can see that everyone is really noisy and colorful.The theme of this music video is really about having fun.
I don't want to try too hard.
I'd like to have fun with it.
Please look forward to the next one!
Ha-ha-ha!
Wow!
What?
Indeed.
I love you
Heart
You can't do hearts.
Oh, I did.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
I love you
Whenever you want more.
You know what you have to do
You know what you have to do.
Bamboo
Bamboo.
Good night.
Come here.
Aaaaaaah!
We're on the air. Please roll the camera.
The music is going.
That girl, too. I'm sure no one else
You look better than me.
I show those feelings when I play.
But when I trust you, I'm scared of betrayal.
You're genuinely kind.
I don't care
I love you
I'm sorry I doubted you.
It's annoying.
I love you
I can't tell you how happy
I've been so happy
I know
I know how happy you were.
I know how happy I was
The dance shot of this song,
Everyone was in a friendly atmosphere, laughing and having fun,
We are having a lot of fun shooting this song.
We will do our best for the next shoot.
I'll do my best.
I like the finger pasta!
Bye bye!
One more time, please.
Bye-bye!
It's okay to slow down, it's okay not to run. Walk and you'll be fine.
Help!
It's more beautiful when you light up a pretty girl's face.
Subscribe to our channel!
Scenery is beautiful.
This single is Takeuchi's last,
But this song is pretty much a graduation, isn't it?But this song is a graduation song.
That's why there are many parts of the music video in which Takeuchi-san is the main character,
I think the last part is a highlight. I think the last part is the highlight of the song, and I think it is unique to this song.
Yes, that's right. We made something by ourselves in the music video,
It's not often that you get to make something by yourself in a music video and then use it as your own decoration in the end.
There were many cases where we were asked to do it from the beginning,
It was the first time for us to participate in such a project, so I think that's something to look forward to.
Oh no, it's okay.
No, I'm okay.
I'm about to cry. I'm going to cry soon.
I'm coming!
I love you. I'm sorry I doubted you.
It's still not a show-off.
Actually, I don't know how happy I was.
How happy I was.
Seino!
How happy I made you.
I'll see you again.
Aaaaah!
I'm sorry I doubted you.
I love you Actually, how much
Yes, I just finished shooting a music video for Alumni...
Um, yes. It will be the last single for me.
I only have a few music video shoots left.
I just finished shooting the music video today, so I hope it will be a great music video for this song.
We just finished shooting today, so I'm looking forward to seeing how it turns out.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it turns out.
I knew when we were filming that it was going to be really great.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the finished product.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how it turns out, and I'm really happy to have such a great song at the end of the day.
I'm really happy to have such a wonderful song at the end.
I hope you will love this song as much as I do.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I watched the music video and thought it was very Angstrom-like, but when I saw the making of the music video, even the voices that are not used in the music video and the voices in the background are very Angstrom-like, with their sparkling smiles and sunny days. It's like they were wearing summery outfits.
I also saw that they made the props by themselves, so I felt that they made the music video by themselves, so I thought it was really wonderful.
Yes, I always thought that everyone in Angulum got along well with each other, but after seeing the behind-the-scenes of this music video shoot, I realized that everyone really had fun filming the music video.
I could feel that everyone really enjoyed shooting the music video, and I thought it was really wonderful.
It was so moving.
It was a very nice music video.
That's all for now. This is the making of the music video shooting of Angulum Alumni.
Angulum: Ai no Kedamono (The Beast of Love)
Thank you for all your hard work.
Next is Beyonce, Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, Vocal Recording
From Beyonce's latest single, Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, here's a look at the vocal recording by Miyo Hirai!
Let's take a shot.
We're going to start with the chorus, so we're going to start with the chorus.
Let's do A and B quickly.
I thought it'd be nice to have an octave down here, too.
A, E, Midnight
This is the way to do it.
I'll take the first and third lines down as well.
A, E, Midnight
I'm sorry about this.
Seriously, there's not much there.
Yes, I'll take only the first half.
I don't get it.This doesn't make any sense. This is not the way to do it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll take out the two doubles on the bottom line.
It doesn't make sense.
There's not a lot of makinsai.
I'll just take the first line.
Yes, sir.
It doesn't make sense.
Okay, let's try one.
I like it. Break the distance.
Don't say "distance" too much.
Break the distance! Break the distance! Break the distance!
Let's make it sound like "Distance," "Distance," "Distance," "Distance," "Distance.
I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay.
And finally, the bar.
Split the distance.
And the bar. I'll aim a little lower.
Split it.
If we go too far, it'll be under the circle.
Bar.
I'll go for about 200 meters.
200 meters apart, close.
Divide the distance.
Hey, no, I like it.
It's okay. It's okay.
And I'm thinking a basic chorus, too.
Shall we shoot the first half first?
Everyone, travelers, read the cruel front first.
Let's call forth a miracle.
That's right. That's it.
Yeah.
Everyone, travellers of destiny, let's call ahead to coincidence, let's call ahead to miracles.
That's what I'm talking about! You're a fast learner! That's it. That's it. That's it. Okay, now, let's do the main one vertically.
Dachitaratta, piratta ladda ladda ladda ladda ladda ladda...
Everyone is a traveler of destiny.
We'll anticipate coincidences, we'll conjure up miracles.
Okay, I got it.
The second half of the song. Let's start with the first part.
Everyone's a traveler of destiny.
♪ Life's all about wanting more, wanting to be happy, wanting to be happy, wanting to be happy.
You got it?
Wait a minute.
Well, we'll just have to get used to it.
Everyone's destined to be a traveler
Everyone's a Destiny's Traveler Life's a quest for more Life's a quest for more Happy, happy, happy
Everyone's a traveler of destiny Life's a quest for more Life's a quest for more happiness
I'm gonna be happy and more happy But I'm not sure how I'm gonna end up.
I don't know if I'm getting there.
I'm not sure we made it to the end.
I'm just trying to make you laugh.
I just want you to laugh
I love this song so much that when I was able to listen to it at an event with Biondo-san the other day, I got really excited,
I didn't know that you had done such a difficult hammory in the recording, and since you always sing so well, I knew that it was such a difficult song to sing,
I was amazed at Mionto's ability to sing such difficult songs.
From the moment I entered Mihiro Hirai's recording booth, I could see Mionto's various expressions, as if she was doing this and that,
I felt like I was watching a play even though it was a recording session. I really enjoyed it.
The above are the vocal recordings of Biondo, Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler, and Hirai Miyo.
Let's work together!
Let's take some pictures, in order.
Yes, ma'am.Yes, sir.
Let's try one.
Take one.
A light rain of luring water is falling A starry forecast for the rest of the day
Sorry to disturb you, but I'll see you today...
After this, that accent
After that... yes, yes, yes...
Let's make it strong there, too.
A light rain is falling, like a star
I'm sorry to disturb you, but I'll see you today.
Let's go with this.
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you...
It's okay.
I love you.
Caw!
Lol.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Don't be shy.
You should be more convincing.
I love you.
I love you, right?
Who talks like that?
When we pass each other.
More, more, more.
It's more casual.
I love you.
It's not like you're saying it casually.
Yes, I love you.
I love you.
Oh, shit.
Mr. Kreit.
That's good.
I'll take some of that.
I'll never use it.
You never know.
I'll go on.
My heart beats so fast
Even the dust before the wind is dancing Jumping with happiness
I've got to dance, I've got to get to the west gate, I've got to get to the west gate, I've got to get there fast
Just a little skip
I'm rushing toward you
Yo yo yo yo
The more my heart flutters
Even the dust before the wind is dancing Jump to happiness
I gotta dance, meet at the west exit ticket gate, I'm rushing toward you
Skip a little
OK, let's try the first chorus
Okay, let's try the first chorus
Let's meet at the west exit ticket gate, we're on our way
Skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, I'm so happy, I'm so stylish
I'm more excited when I'm in a hurry I don't know your armThe suddenness of it, the urgency of it. I don't know about your arms.
I'll take you for a ride tonight, in front of me.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
romance, romance, romance, romance, romance, romance, romance, romance, romance, romance, romance
I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff
Skip, skip, skip, skip
I'll stand out, but I'm still a little behind you, aren't I?
I'm not going to lower it.
I'll keep it right there.
Yes, sir.
And the hotelier was a little bit chewed up, so...
Hotate.
Yes, sir.
Please keep it there.
Hote Tete
Yes, let's go one more time.
Let's meet at the west exit gate and hurry up!
Skip-skip-skip-skip, I'm so happy and stylish
I'm so happy and fashionable!
I'm going to get on the train tonight and stand out in front of you
I'm totally in love with you, love you, love you, temptation, temptation, temptation, temptation
I'll ride it, ride it, ride it, romance, all the way to the factory
I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff, I'm so stiff
Skip, skip, skip, skip
Yes, OK, let's try to get some noise
Let's take the first part of the chorus, skip skip skip
Skip-skip, skip-skip, skip-skip, skip-skip, skip-skip
Skip skip skip skip
Skip skip skip skip skip
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
You don't have to flip your voice over.
Just enough to keep it from flipping over like a normal person.
Skip skip skip skip skip
Let's just do it normally
Skip-skip-skip-skip.
Skip! Skip! Skip Skip Skip! Skip skip skip!
Next, Suki Suki Suki!
Siskiski Siski! You haven't changed!
It's still the same!
Just take a picture with the intention of changing it.
I like it! I like it! I like it!
Okay, I think I got them all!
Okay, I think I got them all! Thank you very much!
Okay! That's it! Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work!
I had an impression of Luna-chan's voice coming out so smoothly from her live performances.
But from the recording session, I could feel that her voice was coming from a deep place.
I think you are really enjoying yourself, seasoning your voice in various ways during the recording process.
You must have a lot of curiosity.
I enjoyed listening to her record one song and felt that she was able to sing the parts that she wasn't singing.
I thought the rhythm of this song was very difficult.
I thought it was great that you sang it so well, and Luna's "I love you" was very personal.
Luna-chan's "I love you" was so cute and touching.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory Skip Skip Skip Yofu Luna's vocal recording.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
Don't worry, I won't kiss you
I couldn't even tell you
Pride Bright July 12 On Scion
Don't worry, we'll manage
Akari Uemura and Nanami Kubota have sent you thick paper It's time to say goodbyeIt's time to say goodbye to the thick paper that Akari Uemura and Nanami Kubota have brought you.
I've seen a lot of videos this time, but I was really moved by Angstrom's "Alumni" and I could feel the goodness inside Angstrom from this making-of video, and I thought it was really wonderful.
I was really impressed by the music video, but the making of the video made me realize the charm of Angstrom in a new way.
I was recording Hirai Miyo and Yobuno Reno's vocals, and I thought that recording really brings out each person's personality.
I thought it was really interesting that the tempo of the person directing the recording was the same, but the atmosphere was completely different.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse of what you don't normally see.
This time upcami is with Akari Uemura of Juice-Juice and Nana Kubota of Ocha no Ma.
Good bye.
Next time on Upokami: "I have to go! The Making of the Music Video Shooting".
and the recording of "Beyonce Yume no Yona Kakeru Yozora ni" (Beyonce Can't Even Draw a Dream in the Night Sky) will be shown.
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel.
undefined